Yen-Yu Chang

881 E El Camino Real, Apt 334, Mountain View, CA, 94040, United States of America

□ (650) 407-7300 | **☑** yenyu@cs.stanford.edu | **ਕ** yuyuchang.github.io | **⊡** yenyuchang | **⑤** rubb9diaw

Research Interests

Deep Learning, Computer Vision, and Computer Graphics

My research interests lie in the general area of machine learning, particularly in deep learning, computer vision, and computer graphics, as well as their applications in object-centric learning, multimodal learning, and neural rendering.

Education

Stanford University

Sep.2019 - Jun.2021 Stanford, California

MASTER OF SCIENCE

- · Major: Electrical Engineering
- Cumulative GPA: 4.00/4.00

National Taiwan University (NTU)

Sep. 2014 - Jun. 2018

Taipei, Taiwan

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN ENGINEERING

- · Major: Electrical Engineering
- Cumulative GPA: 3.86/4.00, Major GPA: 3.87/4.00, CS-Related GPA: 3.95/4.00

Publications _

Point2Cyl: Reverse Engineering 3D Objects - from Point Clouds to Extrusion Cylinders

Mikaela Uy*, <u>Yen-Yu Chang*</u>, Minhyuk Sung, Purvi Goel, Joseph Lambourne, Tolga Birdal, Leonidas Guibas Under Review

ObjectFolder 2.0: A Multisensory Object Dataset for Sim2Real Transfer

Ruohan Gao*, Zilin Si*, <u>Yen-Yu Chang*</u>, Samuel Clarke, Jeannette Bohg, Li Fei-Fei, Wenzhen Yuan, Jiajun Wu UNDER REVIEW

ObjectFolder: A Dataset of Objects with Implicit Visual, Auditory, and Tactile Representations

Ruohan Gao, Yen-Yu Chang*, Shivani Mall*, Li Fei-Fei, Jiajun Wu

May. 2021

PUBLISHED IN THE CONFERENCE ON ROBOT LEARNING 2021 (CORL 2021)

London, UK

Inductive Representation Learning in Temporal Networks via Causal Anonymous Walks | Link

Yanbang Wang, Yen-Yu Chang, Yunyu Liu, Pan Li, and Jure Leskovec

May. 2021

PUBLISHED IN THE 9'TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON LEARNING REPRESENTATIONS (ICLR 2021)

Virtual

F-FADE: Frequency Factorization for Anomaly Detection in Edge Streams | Link

Yen-Yu Chang, Pan Li, Rok Sosic, Mohamed Ibrahim, Marco Schweighauser, and Jure Leskovec Published in The 14'TH ACM International Conference on Web Search and Data Mining (WSDM-2021)

Mar. 2021 Virtual

A Regulation Enforcement Solution for Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning | Link

Fan-Yun Sun, Yen-Yu Chang, Yueh-Hua Wu, and Shou-De Lin

May. 2019

PUBLISHED IN 2019 INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON AUTONOMOUS AGENTS AND MULTIAGENT SYSTEMS (AAMAS-19)

Montreal, Canada

Designing Non-greedy Reinforcement Learning Agents with Diminishing Reward Shaping | Link

Fan-Yun Sun, Yen-Yu Chang, Yueh-Hua Wu, and Shou-De Lin

Feb. 2018

PUBLISHED IN 2018 AAAI/ACM CONFERENCE ON ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE, ETHICS, AND SOCIETY (AIES-18)

New Orleans, USA

ANS: Adaptive Network Scaling for Deep Rectifier Reinforcement Learning Models | Link

Yueh-Hua Wu, Fan-Yun Sun, Yen-Yu Chang, and Shou-De Lin

A Memory-Network Based for Multivariate Time-Series Forecasting | Link

Yen-Yu Chang, Fan-Yun Sun, Yueh-Hua Wu, and Shou-De Lin

PREPRINT

Research Experiences _____

Research Assistant, instructed by Prof. Jiajun Wu, Prof. Fei-Fei Li, & Dr. Ruohan Gao

STANFORD VISION AND LEARNING LAB (SVL)

Feb. 2021 - Present Stanford, California

Researched on multimodal learning and embodied learning with multiple modalities.

- Published the paper "ObjectFolder: A Dataset of Objects with Implicit Visual, Auditory, and Tactile Representations" to CoRL-
- Submitted the paper "ObjectFolder 2.0: A Multisensory Object Dataset for Sim2Real Transfer".

Graduate Researcher, instructed by Prof. Leonidas Guibas

Feb. 2021 - Aug. 2021

STANFORD GEOMETRIC COMPUTATION GROUP

Stanford, California

- Researched on deep learning and 3D computer vision.
- Submitted the paper "Point2Cyl: Reverse Engineering 3D Objects from Point Clouds to Extrusion Cylinders".

Research Assistant, instructed by Prof. Jure Leskovec & Prof. Pan Li

Jul. 2019 - Jan. 2021

STANFORD NETWORK ANALYSIS PROJECT (SNAP)

Stanford, California

- Researched on dynamic graph representation learning, with focus on node classification and link prediction and published the paper
 "Inductive Representation Learning in Temporal Networks via Causal Anonymous Walks" to ICLR-21
- Researched on data mining and social network analysis, with focus on anomaly detection and published the paper "F-FADE: Frequency Factorization for Anomaly Detection in Edge Streams" to WSDM-21.

Undergraduate Researcher, instructed by Prof. Hung-Yi Lee & Prof. Lin-Shan Lee

Feb. 2017 - Jun. 2018

SPEECH PROCESSING AND MACHINE LEARNING LABORATORY, DEPARTMENT OF ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING, NTU

Taipei, Taiwan

Researched on natural language processing, with focus on visual question answering.

Undergraduate Researcher, instructed by Prof. Shou-de Lin

Jul. 2016 - Jun. 2018

Machine Discovery and Social Network Mining Laboratory, Department of Computer Science and Information

Taipei, Taiwan

- Engineering. NTU
- Researched on reinforcement learning and multi-agent system, with focus on collaborative and ethics behaviors and published the paper "Designing Non-greedy Reinforcement Learning Agents with Diminishing Reward Shaping" to AIES-19.
 Researched on reinforcement learning and multi-agent system, with focus on learning agent-to-agent interaction and published the
- Researched on reinforcement learning and multi-agent system, with focus on learning agent-to-agent interaction and published the
 paper "A Regulation Enforcement Solution for Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning" as the extended abstract to AAMAS 2019.
- Participated in KDD Cup 2018 and achieved 19th place in main prize and 4th place in special prize.

Undergraduate Researcher, instructed by Prof. Ho-Lin Chen

Jul. 2015 - Jul. 2017

GAME THEORY AND MOLECULAR COMPUTING LABORATORY, DEPARTMENT OF ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING, NTU

Taipei, Taiwan

- Researched on game theory, with focus on network creation games and price of anarchy (PoA).
- Proved the upper bound of PoA for all Heterogeneous Star Celebrity Games. Link

Selected Projects

Dynamic Graph networks for anomalous behavior detection in social network system

Sep. 2019 - Dec. 2020

FOR STANFORD NETWORK ANALYSIS PROJECT

- Design new dynamic graph network to model higher-order dependencies between nodes
- Analyze anomalous behaviors in social network systems

Long-term Air Quality Forecasting

Mar. 2018 - Jun. 2018

FOR CSIE7433 (MACHINE LEARNING: THEORY AND PRACTICE)

- Built a recurrent neural network model to forecast air quality in future 48 hours and applied forecast weather data in our RNN.
- 19th place in KDD Cup 2018 and 4th place in KDD Cup 2018 special prize

Honors & Awards _

INTERNATIONAL

2018 **19th Place (out of 4180 teams)**, KDD Cup 2018

London, U.K.

2018 4th Place (out of 4180 teams), KDD Cup 2018 Special Prize

London, U.K.

DOMESTIC

2016 **Dean's List**, GPA in top 5% in Department of Electrical Engineering, NTU

Taipei, Taiwan

Skills_

Languages Python, C/C++, Shell scripting, Matlab

Libraries/Tools Keras, Tensorflow, Pytorch

OS GNU/Linux (Ubuntu & Arch Linux), Mac OSX

Other Git, MTFX